<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blockchain on ZKBR</title>
    <link>https://zkbr.github.io/tags/blockchain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blockchain on ZKBR</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:19:14 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zkbr.github.io/tags/blockchain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zkbr.github.io/project/benchmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:19:14 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zkbr.github.io/project/benchmark/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Verifiable computation outsourcing has become a critical tool in various applications, particularly in scaling blockchain networks like Ethereum. A prominent example is the use of rollups, a layer-2 scaling solution designed to increase Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s transaction throughput. In this approach, transactions are offloaded to a secondary layer that mirrors Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s functionality but operates on a high-performance cluster. To maximize efficiency, hundreds of transactions are batched, compressed, and processed together. The resulting state of this layer-2 ledger is then computed and submitted to the Ethereum mainnet for verification and permanent record-keeping.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zkbr.github.io/project/cbdc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:19:07 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zkbr.github.io/project/cbdc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Central banks worldwide are exploring the use of blockchain technology to issue and manage digital versions of fiat currencies, known as Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs). However, this endeavor faces significant challenges. While most blockchain systems lack robust privacy protections, those that do offer privacy often do not support smart contracts, which are essential for enabling programmable money and advanced financial applications. Additionally, there is a need to balance privacy with regulatory requirements, such as allowing law enforcement to access transaction data under specific circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
